http://www.wups.com/pages/website-privacy-policy

Login/Register
Email Address:
Password:
Forgot Password
Login
Not a Member? Sign up here!
Keyword
Go
Website Privacy Statement
Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us.
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our radio station homepages and at every
point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on any Black Diamond Broadcastingstation website, as represented in our logo above. On some pages, you can make requests and/or register to enter contest giveaways. The types of personal information collected at these pages might include
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself for our purpose only. We do not share this information with outside parties.  We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties. You can register with our websites if you would like to receive our station newsletters as well as updates on our promotions, events and contests. Information you submit on our websites will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment to Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our Commitment to Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by writing to:
Black Diamond Website Security
c/o Social Media Director
514 Munson Ave Traverse City, MI 49686
We use this procedure to better safeguard your information. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.  To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
How to Contact Us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call or email us at
231-922-4981
social@blackdiamondbroadcasting.com
Listen On Alexa!
on Michigan adventures. Tap Image for your very own PDF copy!
If you need help accessing the online public file due to a disability, please contact us
Home  |  WUPS Public File  |  Web Privacy  |  Employment Opportunities  |  Advertising Information  |  Contact Us
© 2020 WUPS-FM, Black Diamond Broadcast Group LLC.
Built on Envisionwise Technology.
